lasd.org 2014-12-16

# LASD.org - Information Detail

The Board of Supervisors of Los Angeles County recognizes the public's concern about privacy on the Internet. This privacy statement establishes how information gathered about you from your visit to our Website will be used by this Website's operators. As a visitor, however, you should be aware that much information submitted to the Los Angeles County Sheriff Department is public information under the laws of the State of California. Under some circumstances, we may be required to disclose such information in accordance with the California Public Records Act or other legal requirements.The following describes how information may be collected depending on your activities at this Website: **If you read or download information:** We may collect and store information for statistical purposes. For example, we may count the number of visitors to the different sections of our site to help us make them more useful. The information collected may include such items as the name and domain of the host from which you access the Internet, the Internet Protocol (IP) address of the computer you are using or your browser software and operating system. This information does not identify you personally. **If you send E-mail to this Website:** By sending us an electronic mail message, you may be sending us personally identifiable (i.e., your name, address, e-mail address, etc.). We may store the name and address of the requester in order to respond to the request or otherwise resolve the subject matter of your e-mail. You should know that e-mail is not necessarily secure against interception and may be subject to the disclosure requirements of the Public Records Act or other legal disclosure requirements. **If you fill out a form or submit an application or request other specific information:** The Los Angeles County Sheriff Department may ask visitors who request specific information to fill out a form. For example, when requesting information about a crime report, civil process, weapon permits, or other subjects, the visitors may be asked to provide their names, addresses, e-mail addresses and other pertinent information to ensure we can process and deliver the information requested. Other information may be collected at these sites through questionnaires, feedback forms or other means to enable us to determine a visitor's interests with the goal of providing better service. **If you use this Website to make a purchase, deposit or payment:** The applicable Credit Card Disclosure linked below describes how personally identifiable information is treated in connection with making a purchase, deposit or payment. If you are using this Website to deposit money in an inmate's trust account, please see the Credit Card Disclosure. The Credit Card Disclosures are incorporated into the body of this Privacy Policy by this reference. For specific information please refer to LASD Credit Card Disclosure here: [ http://shq.lasdnews.net/pages/PageDetail.aspx?id=1961 ](http://shq.lasdnews.net/pages/PageDetail.aspx?id=1961)**Consequences of failing to provide information:** If you choose not to provide us with the information described above for us to refer, respond to, or investigate the issue you are concerned about. **Sharing information:** We may share personally identifiable information with other Los Angeles County Departments or Law Enforcement agencies in the course of carrying out our normal business operations.We may disclose information about inmates, wanted suspects, missing persons, etc. as required in the normal course of our duties. **Links to non-Los Angeles County (third party) Websites:** Our Website also contains links to information located on Websites maintained by other public agencies and private organizations. Once you access an individual document that links you to another Website, you are subject to the privacy policy of the Website containing that document. **Gaining access to information and providing corrections:** For information on how to review and/or make changes to information we have received from you online and may have stored, contact this department through the email address or telephone number noted on our web site. If you find that this information is inaccurate or incomplete, you may provide us with verified accurate and complete information. **Information transmitted by user is not secure from interception:** We take several measures to protect the transmission of the information you submit to us when you use our web site. However, there is a possibility that information transmitted to us over the Internet may be intercepted by a third party.If you choose to send us email, or fill out an on-line form on our web site, you should know that the information is not necessarily secure against interception, and may be subject to the disclosure requirements of the California Public Records Act or other legal disclosure requirements **Disclaimer of Liability:** With respect to information available from this web page, neither the County of Los Angeles Sheriff Department nor any of its employees make any warranty, express or implied, including the warranty of merchant ability and fitness for a particular purpose, or assume any liability or responsibility for the accuracy, completeness, or usefulness of such information.
